♪♪～
Uh, Gin-san?
What is it, Shinpachi?
Just to be clear, what was that countdown
you mentioned in the preview last week?
《銀時:早くしてくれ…｡
頼むから… 早くやってくれ｡
Was it just the usual...?
Another fake ending scam?
お願いだ…
早く… ｵﾚにとどめを刺してくれ｡
Of course not.
We're actually having
a countdown today.
I'm a grown-up. I'm not
going to lie every time.
なぜ
ひと思いにとどめを刺さない｡
It's a matter of trust.
なぜ 時間を稼ぐ…｡
You think that people
still trust this show?
殺せよ！
やるなら ｻｯｻとやりやがれ!!
Ouch, Kagura-chan!
Where did you learn to be so hateful?!
ｵﾚをもてあそんで
そんなに楽しいか ﾃﾒｴら！
You can't blame them, Gin-san.
頼むよ！ こうして ただ黙って➡
We said we're entering the "final chapter"
around the same time last year.
忍び寄る死を待つのは
つらすぎんだよ！
That means we've been in the "final
chapter" for a whole year.
気がおかしくなりそうなんだよ！
なぁ お願いだ！
Plus there was the whole fake last episode
fiasco at the end of our third year.
早く… 早くｵﾚを殺してくれ!!》
Oh, that.
Well, they just wanted to try
out some last episode gag.
あの坂田さん… すみませんけど
お静かにしてもらえます？
It wasn't meant to trick the audience.
We figured that everybody was used
to the show's style by now, but...
他の患者さんの ご迷惑なんで｡
The phones at TV Tokyo were ringing non-stop
right from the start of that episode.
すみません｡
And because I made an ambiguous
statement about Sunrise,
"Sunrise" became the number
one searched term on the net.
《ｲﾔだ… ｲﾔだよ 歯医者｡
The script actually had me saying
that Sunrise went bankrupt.
この独特なﾆｵｲ…
いかがわしい ｲｰｼﾞｰﾘｽﾆﾝｸﾞ｡
Naturally, we got called by the producers'
higher-ups at the time and got yelled at.
"Do you have any idea what it means
to be a publicly traded company?!"
鳴り響くﾄﾞﾘﾙ音｡
Even the staff got a call from their families who
were watching the show and were asked,
そして 死刑執行を待つような
この待ち時間｡
"It looks like GinTama is ending.
Do you have another job lined up?"
ｲﾔだ 超帰りてえ！
今すぐ帰って➡
定春に抱きつきてえ！
ﾓﾌﾓﾌしてえ！
Why would you want to trick your family?
でも歯 痛いし でも治療怖えし｡
Yeah, yeah. I get it already. We're sorry.
もう何巡目だ
こんなこと考えんのは｡
That's why we're actually having
a countdown today.
頼むから
もう ｻｯｻと とどめ刺してくれ｡
No lies, I swear!
Are you sure?
確かに 甘い物好きと虫歯は
切っても切れない縁だけれども➡
Is the GinTama anime really
having a countdown?
Really! Look at my eyes!
最近は すっかりそんな設定
忘れられてたじゃん｡
Do I look like I'm lying?
全然 甘いもん食べるｼｰﾝなんか
なかったじゃん｡
Sorry, we've only got a background
shot, so I can't tell.
絶対 削られるよな｡
絶対 ﾄﾞﾘﾙ 口に突っ込まれるよな｡
So let's begin the GinTama
anime countdown!
Coming up next!
ﾄﾞﾘﾙなんて普通
口に突っ込むもんじゃねえよ｡
Did he just dismiss me?!
いちばん
突っ込んじゃいけないもんだよ｡
医者のやっていいことじゃねえよ｡
どうしよう…
もし ﾄﾞﾘﾙ突っ込まれてるときに➡
ｸｼｬﾐとかしちゃったら死ぬのかな｡
ｵﾚ 死ぬのかな｡
どうしよう… もし削りｶｽとか
ﾂﾊﾞとか吸い込む あの機械に➡
["Countdown Begins"]
舌とか巻き込まれたら死ぬのかな｡
ｵﾚ 死んじゃうのかな》
Wow! Good evening to everyone
watching Countdown GinTama!
Huh? What is this?
あぁ～！
やめやめ！ もうやめ～!!
Thank you for sending in your votes!
Wh-Why're we CGI?
Now let's get right to it!
《余計なこと考えるのは
もうやめよう｡
Number one for the best GinTama
lines ranking is...
雑誌でも読んで気を紛らわそう｡
｢ｼﾞｬﾝﾌﾟ｣… ｢ｼﾞｬﾝﾌﾟ｣…｡
Count...
Down!
なんだ ここ ｢まがじん｣派かぁ｡
まぁ たまにはいいか…》
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #1]
Gintoki Sakata... You are a ghost.
You once tried to protect this country
along with Shinsuke and the others.
ﾔﾆでも取りに来たのか？ ﾆｺ中｡
(土方)ﾂﾗ見りゃわかんだろ｡
You are obsessed and unable to let go.
昔 詰めた銀歯の奥が
知らねえうちに腐ってたんだよ｡
まったく
銀のつくﾔﾂに ろくなもんはねえ｡
You are a living ghost!
離せよ 先に取ったのｵﾚだろ｡
There is no longer anything
for you to protect!
いや 同時だ｡
そもそも ﾃﾒｴ ｢ｼﾞｬﾝﾌﾟ｣派だろ｡
ここは｢まがじん｣派のｵﾚに譲れよ｡
Ghosts should go back
where they belong.
たまには敵情を観察することも
大切なんだよ｡
創刊50周年だか
なんだか知らねえけど➡
｢ｻﾝﾃﾞｰ｣と組んで
なに悪だくみしてんだよ｡
こざかしいんだよ ﾃﾒｴら｡
なに妬いてんの？
I'll play a requiem!
仲間に入りたいの？ ﾊﾟｰﾃｨｰに
入れなかったのが悔しいの？
全然 勝手にやれば？ ｵﾚたちは
１人のほうが全然 気楽だし➡
つるむとか嫌いだし
眼中にねえし お前らなんて｡
The strings...!
眼中にねえのは こっちなんだよ｡
嫌われてるのわかんないの？
Hey, tough guy!
お前ら…
はじかれてるのわかんないの？
Take off those headphones, dammit!
あの お静かに｡
他の患者さんが…｡
｢ｻﾝﾃﾞｰ｣は ｢まがじん｣の
友達のﾌﾘしてるだけだよ｡
When did he get ahold of my strings?
What're you waiting for? Fire!
こないだ学校 一緒に帰ってるとき
ﾒｯﾁｬ悪口言ってたから｡
｢ｻﾝﾃﾞｰ｣が
そんなことするわけねえだろ｡
いいかげんなこと言ってんじゃ…｡
じゃあ ｢ﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝ｣に聞いてみろよ｡
Clean out your ears and listen up!
ｱｲﾂも聞いてたから｡
うるせえよ！
I've never once fought for the
sake of this cheap country.
ﾃﾒｴに ｢ｻﾝﾃﾞｰ｣の何がわかんだよ！
かりそめの仲よしごっご➡
やってればいいじゃん！
ﾎﾝﾄは全然 仲よくないくせに｡
おい うるせえって言ってんだろ
ﾃﾒｴら！
I couldn't care less...
if this country or samurai
fell. I have always...
《ｲﾔなﾔﾂと会っちまったぜ…》
Then, and now...
What I protect...
《よりによって こんな所で
鉢合わせしちまうなんざ…》
《平静を装わなければ…》
has never changed!
《ｺｲﾂにだけは 弱みを
握られるわけにはいかねえ》
《２人:いい歳こいて
歯医者が苦手なんて➡
Okay!
So number one in the "Best GinTama Line
Ranking" was Gintoki Sakata with,
絶対 知られたくねえ！》
"Then, and now, what I protect
has never changed!"
おい… ちょっと さっきから
いいかげんにしてくんない？
Man, I'm awesome.
ｿﾜｿﾜ ｿﾜｿﾜ
何回 足を組み替えてんだよ｡
The main characters in a
JUMP Anime always rule.
Even machine gun bullets
were swerving around me.
なんか
こっちも落ち着かねえだろ おい｡
Now hold it right there!
お前こそ何だよ さっきから
貧乏揺すり ﾊﾝﾊﾟねえんだけど｡
I mean, this...
This really is just a Count Down TV!!
[Note: Count Down TV. A late night Japanese music ranking
show that is hosted by CG animated characters.]
Yep! Gin-san never lies!
やめてくんない？ 貧乏がうつる｡
ﾃﾒｴのｿﾜｿﾜに ｲﾗついてんだろうが｡
Fine, you didn't lie,
but you still tricked the audience!
あれ？ ひょっとしてあれかなぁ
ﾋﾞﾋﾞってらっしゃるんですか？
We got caught up in the flow
and yelled "Down!" with you.
鬼の副長ともあろうお方が｡
え？ 何が？ 意味がわかんない｡
Is this the annual recap episode that we do
right before the start of the Fall season?
何にﾋﾞﾋﾞるの？ 歯医者で
何か怖いことってあったっけ？
Exactly.
いや別に～｡ 何もないけど｡
Man, we always manage to burn through the
budget for the first two quarters by this time.
怖いことがあると思ってるから
そういう発想になるんだろう？
ﾋﾞﾋﾞってんの お前じゃねえの？
んなわけないじゃん｡
So we have to throw in a recap episode.
Will you stop with the graphic
production details?
ほら よく言うじゃん
ﾄﾞﾘﾙの音が怖いだのなんだのと｡
We had a teensy bit of budget left over,
so we were able to do this CG.
ｵﾚには まったくわからねえけど｡
ｵﾚも まったくわからねえな｡
Well, that's only natural after all the
alternate route bonuses we used.
むしろ 毎週
ﾄﾞﾘﾙ突っ込んでほしいぐらいだし｡
定期的に歯垢とか
取りに来たいくらいだから｡
That's right!
The entire fourth year of the GinTama anime is like
a bonus that came with the previous three years.
あれ？ お前やってないの？
ｵﾚなんか もう３日にいっぺん➡
ﾄﾞﾘってもらってるけどね｡ 口の中
気持悪くてしゃあないよね｡
Don't be so brutal!
Well, back to the subject at hand.
ﾄﾞﾘらないと… うん｡
We'll continue with the best lines ranking!
あぁ そうなんだ｡
ｵﾚは自宅に ﾏｲﾄﾞﾘﾙあるから➡
And when was the poll
for this even done?
通う必要はないんだよね｡
ﾄﾞﾘﾗｰだからさ ｵﾚ｡
It was a legitimate vote...
《ﾄﾞﾘﾗｰ!? なに ﾄﾞﾘﾗｰって！
In Shonen JUMP...
How long ago was that?!
なんで ﾏｲﾄﾞﾘﾙなんて
持ってんだよ！
Count...
ｺｲﾂ ﾊﾝﾊﾟねえ！
まったく ﾄﾞﾘﾙに ﾋﾞﾋﾞってねえ！》
Down!
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #2]
なんだよ お前も
ﾄﾞﾘﾗｰだったのか 奇遇だな｡
You idiot!
今度 あれだったら
一緒にﾄﾞﾘﾙｺﾝﾃｽﾄでも出てみねえ？
Why do you always put all
the burden on yourself?
《ﾄﾞﾘﾙｺﾝﾃｽﾄ～!?
やだ 出たくねえ そんな大会！
So you plan on being the bad
guy all by yourself too?
ｺｲﾂ そんなもんに出場してたのか｡
なんて恐ろしい野郎だ！》
I know how you feel, Toshi...
あぁ 休日が合えばな｡
まぁ 空けるようにしとくよ｡
...About Mitsuba-dono!
(長谷川)あれ？ 仲の悪い２人が
こんなところで何やってんだ？
長谷川さん｡
なんだ お前たちも
歯やっちまったのか？
(土方)あぁ まぁ ちょっと
散歩がてら ﾄﾞﾘりにな｡
What a pity.
(長谷川)ﾄﾞﾘり？ なんだ それ｡
長谷川さんも ﾄﾞﾘりに？
I'm sure Mitsuba will be sad, too.
To lose one of her old friends.
ﾄﾞﾘっていうか まぁ 治療にな｡
小便したくて ちょっと
抜けてきたとこなんだけどよ｡
I really wanted to be on good
terms with you people.
いやぁ まいったわ｡
If I got the backing of the Shinsengumi,
ここの治療… 超痛えぞ｡
then I could run my business
without any restrictions.
That's why I approached one of your relatives
and even set out to marry her,
へ へぇ そうなんだ｡
ｵﾚ 何か月も ﾀﾞﾗﾀﾞﾗ
歯医者通うのｲﾔだからさ｡
but who knew she was that sick?
ここなら１回の治療で
済むって聞いてきたんだけど｡
So from the start, you just used
her to get us on your side?
いや 治療は早いけど
痛いのなんのって｡
I loved her.
ｵﾚ 何回 声あげそうになったか
わからねえよ｡
As a merchant, I love things
that will make me a profit.
長谷川さん！
まだですか？
あぁ すみません！ 今行きます！
But only as a tool.
じゃ 行くわ｡ ｵﾒｴらも
覚悟かためといたほうがいいぜ｡
I just want her to taste a bit of happiness
like other people before she dies.
そ そうか 痛いのか…｡
まぁ でも 歯の治療は
痛くて当たり前だしな｡
そ そうだね｡
逆に痛くないと➡
ﾎﾝﾄ これで治ったの？ って
不安になるからな｡
I won't call you a bastard.
あれ？ なんか顔色悪くねえ？
I'm no better.
いや 全然｡
(長谷川)ｷﾞｬ～!!
I've done more than my
share of bad things.
長谷川さん
あまり暴れないでください｡
And to top it off, I'm trying to kill
the husband of a dying woman.
危ないから じっとしてて｡
(薮田)ちょっと長谷川さん｡
押さえつけて｡
Sad, isn't it?
ﾍﾞﾙﾄで ｲｽに縛りつけて｡
あぁ そうそう そんな感じ｡
So you can say, we're like two of a kind.
《なんか 尋常じゃないくらい
苦しんでるんだけど…》
No wonder they call you
the demon Vice-Chief.
《いったい
どんな治療してんだ!?》
I think you and I will get along well.
先生 長谷川さんの脈が！
That's really...
(薮田)心臓ﾏｯｻｰｼﾞして｡
あれだったら 電気ｼｮｯｸ｡
...an exaggeration.
《電気ｼｮｯｸ!? なんで
歯医者で そんなもん必要!?》
先生 脈は戻りましたけど
衝撃で ｱﾚがとれました｡
《ｱﾚがとれた!? ｱﾚって何だよ！
何がとれたんだ？》
I just...
...want the girl I love to be happy.
(薮田)あぁ 大丈夫｡ もうそれ
使わないから ﾎﾟﾝ酢につけて｡
《ﾎﾟﾝ酢につける!?
何やってんだ いったい！》
Boy, Hijikata-san's great.
先生 これは どっちかというと
ごまﾀﾞﾚのほうが合いますね｡
He knows how to be a man.
That was awesome.
《ごまﾀﾞﾚ？
しゃぶしゃぶやってんの？
Huh?
これ しゃぶしゃぶだよね!?》
Gin-san? You seem to have
a problem with the ranking.
(薮田)よし だいたい終わりかな｡
Damn right I do!
《終わりなの!?
ﾎﾟﾝ酢でしめたよ！》
Sheesh, why is he in second?
(薮田)どうですか？ 長谷川さん｡
He might act all cool and all, but he's just
another comic relief character now!
(長谷川)いや ｳｿみたいに
痛みがとれましたね｡
That's right.
《痛みどころか なんか
人体の一部がとれたらしいよ｡
Between his mayo obsession
and Toshi,
any serious line from him ends
up sounding like a joke!
ﾎﾟﾝ酢で いかれたらしいよ！》
(薮田)これで 以前のように
何でも食べられますから｡
Right!
Uh, you people have no right
to say that to Hijikata-san.
(長谷川)いやぁ
ありがとうございました 先生｡
Besides, his best lines would be like:
これ 痛み止めと➡
特別に うちで作った
歯ﾌﾞﾗｼつけときますから｡
We've run out of mayonnaise!!
あぁ すみません｡
気遣ってもらって｡
Live happily, mayo!
じゃあ お大事に！
ありがとうございました！
I-It...
It's stuck!
いやぁ すっかり治ったぜ！
Finally, I've got enough mayonnaise!
ﾒﾁｬｸﾁｬ痛かったけど
なかなかいい歯医者だったよ｡
You two really are evil.
ほら 親切に
歯ﾌﾞﾗｼまでつけてくれたし｡
That was a horrible selection!
Well, I feel much better now, so here's
the best line ranking, count...
《２人:つけとくって どこに!?》
Down!
《待て！ 歯が治ったかわりに➡
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #3]
それ以上 大事なﾓﾝ
持ってかれてるじゃねえか！》
《等価交換どころの
騒ぎじゃねえよ！》
歯ﾌﾞﾗｼが ﾊﾞｻﾊﾞｻになったら
また取り替えにきてくださいね｡
ちょっと
言いたいことがあるんですが…｡
《そうだよ言え！ ｸﾚｰﾑつけろ！》
《とんでもねえﾔﾌﾞ医者だよ》
ｵﾚ 毛質硬めじゃないと
磨いた気にならないんですけど｡
《２人:そこじゃねえだろ！》
あぁ 大丈夫ですよ｡
予備で 股間にも
歯ﾌﾞﾗｼつけときましたから｡
そっちは いじくってたら
なんか硬くなります｡
《｢硬くなります｣じゃねえ！
そんなとこで➡
どうやって歯磨くんだ！
奥さんしか磨けねえだろ！》
(薮田)はい じゃあ お大事にね｡
(近藤)おぉ ﾄｼじゃねえか！
お前たちも治療に来てたのか！
近藤さん｡
いや なかなか➡
いい歯医者だった！
すっかり治っちまったよ！
おまけに 特別に
電動歯ﾌﾞﾗｼまでつけてくれてな｡
So this is the end of the line?
《電動歯ﾌﾞﾗｼっていうか…》
Rather than be caught by the enemy,
《それ ただの
長谷川さんの手じゃね？》
let us finish as warriors
and slash our bellies.
ちょっと ﾎﾟﾝ酢くせえんだけど
かなり使えるよね これは｡
《おい！ 完全に
長谷川さんのだろ！》
Don't be stupid.
そうか？ なんでも➡
機械に頼るってやり方は
ｵﾚは好きじゃないな｡
Stand up.
やっぱ 歯くらいは
自分の手で磨かないと｡
《いや それがお前の手だから｡
つ～か すでに お前の手
歯ﾌﾞﾗｼになってるし！》
If you've got enough time to fantasize
about your beautiful death,
長谷… 電動歯ﾌﾞﾗｼが腐ったら
また取り替えにきてくださいね｡
why don't you live your life
beautifully to the end?
《今 長谷川さんの腕って
言いかけたよね!?》
Huh?
すみません
あの… この電動歯ﾌﾞﾗｼ➡
Those lines sounded familiar,
ｲﾏｲﾁ 口元に届かないんですけど
大丈夫ですか？
but we've never seen
those images on TV?
Zura and Gin-chan seemed
really high quality too.
大丈夫です｡ 届かなかったら➡
自分の手で 歯ﾌﾞﾗｼを持って
磨いてください｡
No worries. No worries.
《だったら なんでつけたんだ！
ただの嫌がらせじゃねえか！》
And don't be concerned about footage from
last year's anime tour being mixed in.
じゃあ ２人とも お大事に｡
Wait! Are we okay with this?!
Doesn't that involve a bunch of copyright
issues and other stuff we can't mention?!
《お大事にじゃねえだろ！
お前らが患者を大事にしろ！》
It's fine.
The producers are in their suits and
explaining it to everybody right now.
《歯治すどころか あんなもん
ただの改造手術じゃねえか！》
It's not fine then!
《やばい… この歯医者
やばすぎる！》
Then we'll continue the ranking
after the commercials!
ひぃ～！
This will keep dragging on.
《お おい 何やってんだよ
ﾃﾒｴ さっさと帰れよ｡
Good evening to everyone watching
Count Down GinTama.
This is Hitomi Takahashi and...
ここは もう歯医者なんかじゃねえ
ただのｼｮｯｶｰ本部だぞ》
The BEAT CRUSADERS!
《意地張ってねえで 帰れよ｡
Our single did well in the Oricon ranking,
so thanks for your support!
ねぇ 何やってんの？
帰ってお願い 300円あげるから》
And in closing, please listen to our song!
《何なんだよ ｺｲﾂ！
なんで逃げねえんだ!?》
Wo ai ni!
《空気読めよ ｺﾗ｡
お前が帰らねえと
ｵﾚも帰れねえんだよ ﾊﾞｶ野郎！》
じゃ 次の患者さん
入ってください ２人ずつ｡
《えっ おい ｳｿだろ!?》
《ﾏ ﾏｼﾞでいくの!?》
さあて 今回のﾄﾞﾘﾙは どこまで
ｵﾚの中にえぐり込んでこれるか➡
ｵﾚの魂にまで届くかなぁ｡
《ｲﾔだ！ 行きたくねえ！
何？ 魂に届くﾄﾞﾘﾙって｡
言ってて 全然意味わかんねえ》
人はなぜ 穴を掘り進むのか？
そこに ﾄﾞﾘﾙがあるからさ｡
《何それ!? ﾊﾞｶなの？
ｵﾚは ﾊﾞｶなの？
男の意地なんて どうでもいいから
さっさと逃げろ！》
《おい～ 誰か～！》
《誰か…》
《２人:ｵﾚたちを止めてくれ～！》
♪♪～
(薮田)どうも｡ 南無歯科医院の
薮田です｡
坂田さんと 土方さんね
よろしくお願いしますね｡
ﾊﾊﾊ そんなに
かたくならないでよ｡
痛くしませんから｡
まっ 気楽にかけて｡
ほら かけて｡
《２人:さ 殺人現場!?》
《治療室って こんなに
真っ赤だったっけ？
もっと白くなかったっけ？
もっと
清潔な感じじゃなかった!?》
《歯の治療って
こんなに出血したっけ？
もっと こぢんまりした道具が
並んでなかったっけ？
ﾁｪｰﾝｿｰとか あったっけ!?》
《２人:歯医者って
こんなんだったっけ～!?》
A big thank you to Miss Hitomi Takahashi
and the BEAT CRUSADERS!
あぁ ２人とも
だいぶ腫れちゃってるね｡
どうして こんなになるまで
放置してたの？
Uh, how is this show even considered
an anime at this point?
ﾀﾞﾒだよ 口っていうのは
いわば 人間の玄関だからね｡
Wrong!
[Note: Referring to the stunt they
pulled back in Episode #165]
After Gintamikey, there
are no boundaries!
人となりを知る 入り口という
意味でもあるのよ｡
You have a point.
歯をみれば その人がどんなんか
だいたい わかるからね うん｡
Then we'll continue with the Best
GinTama Lines Ranking!
We'll play the fourth, fifth, and
sixth place clips together!
やっぱりね 歯が汚い人は
だらしない人が多い｡
Count...
Down!
歯を きれいに管理してる人は➡
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #4-6]
親のしつけも
行き届いた人が多いよね うん｡
だから 若い患者さんが来たときは
いっつも こう言ってるのよ｡
合ｺﾝやるときは 相手の顔とか
ｷｬﾗより まず…➡
He did pretty well for a human.
おっぱいを見ろってね｡
《２人:先生
玄関ﾄﾞｱ外れてます～！》
Hey, big fella.
It'll take more than a blow like
that...to break my soul!
おっぱい見たら 人となりも
わかるしね うん｡
You're finished now, bastards.
《土方:やっぱり 全然
ちゃんとしてねえよ 先生｡
最終的に おっぱいの話してるし》
You've made an enemy of
the entire Harusame gang!
《ﾄﾞｱ外れてるどころか 玄関から
便所みてえなﾆｵｲが放たれてるよ｡
Soon, Harusame from throughout
the universe will come to kill you.
玄関入って そっこう
便所のﾆｵｲがした➡
丹羽君ちみたいになってるよ！
便器が玄関だよ あれ！》
Yeah? So what? You won't
be around to see it.
Listen... I don't care what you do
somewhere else in the universe,
あぁ あと 乳輪が小さい女は
ｶﾞﾝｶﾞﾝ束縛してくるよね➡
要注意だよね｡
but anywhere within reach of my sword,
《誰も お前なんて
束縛しねえよ！》
とにかく 女は乳輪だね｡
あとは どうでもいいね うん｡
is my country!
《つうか 乳輪が見える合ｺﾝって➡
いったい どんな合ｺﾝに
参加してたんだよ!?》
Don't you understand?
This is what you call a battle of
vengeance. Avenging a killer?
さて じゃあ そろそろ
治療始めましょうか｡
There's nothing to gain. I know that.
２人とも とりあえず 助手に
かるく診せるから｡
まっ 助手たちでもどうにかなる
程度かもしれないしね｡
But if I don't do anything now, I
won't be able to live with myself.
《た 助かった｡
ｺｲﾂが治療すんじゃねえのか》
Cut it out already!
お～い ちょっと そこの２人！
Stupid curlyhead!
Wh-Wh-What's wrong, Kagura-chan?
は～い｡
はい｡
After all that complaining
about the mayo freak,
we end up with all these examples
of you saying serious stuff!
中山さん 戦闘妖精ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝさん
どっちが診たい？
Are you okay with that?
《中山さ～ん！》
《断固 中山さん！》
You don't care if this GinTama ranking
is filled only with serious lines?!
《ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝさんだけは 勘弁しろ～》
え～ どうしよう｡
どっちが好み？
Y-Yeah, but...
I didn't make this ranking.
私は 黒髪のほうかな？
This was the united opinion of
everybody watching GinTama.
《土方:つうか 何だ!? あれ｡
なんで 戦闘妖精ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝが➡
歯医者にいんだ!? つうか
戦闘妖精ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝって何だ!?》
Right, Shinpachi?
No, Kagura-chan's exactly right.
おたくらは どっちに診てもら…｡
(２人)中山さんがいいです！
I can't accept this.
And I doubt any of my lines
are going to show up.
あぁ ちょっと 坂田さんのほうが
早かったね｡
Hey, four-eyes!
Don't backstab me!
じゃあ 坂田さん 中山さんね｡
(土方)待って！ ちょっと待って！
It'll feel more like GinTama
with a little editing.
Then we'll do fourth, fifth, and
sixth place again. Count...
よっしゃ～！ 助かった！
Down!
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #4-6]
中山です
よろしくお願いしますね坂田さん｡
It'll take more than a blow like
that...to break my XXX!
《ｵ ｵﾒｴが 中山かよ～!?
待て！ ちょっと待て！
but anywhere within reach of my XXX,
お前は どう見ても
戦闘妖精ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝだろ!?
どう見ても
中山さんじゃねえだろ!?》
is my XXX!
《ﾌﾌﾌ ざまあみろ｡
But if I don't do anything now,
よくわからんが こっちの助手が➡
I won't be XXX to XXX with myself.
戦闘妖精ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝさん
だったようだな》
Hey!
あ あの よろしくお願いします
ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝさん｡
My awesome lines!
If you beep those parts,
♪♪～
it'll sound like I'm saying
something obscene!
That's the Gin-chan we know and love!
Hell no, you XXX!
Yeah, censoring words and images
is one of the basics of GinTama.
戦闘妖精ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝです
よろしくお願いします｡
Shut up, Ganbarist!
[Note: Referring to the 1996 Anime "Ganbarist! Shun". The title character was voiced by Shinpachi's voice actor.]
Who are you calling Ganbarist?!
《なんでだ～!?》
And now to the seventh and eight place,
along with the censored collection,
じゃ 中山さん ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝさん
がんばってね～！
(２人)ﾗｼﾞｬｰ｡
《結局 中山さんも ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝさんも
戦闘妖精じゃねえか！》
set to Otsu-chan's music! Here we go!
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #7-8]
では 治療の前に 当医院の
ｼｽﾃﾑについて➡
説明させてもらいます｡
《そんな説明の前に まず
お前らが どうして➡
If I stop now, my XXXX will break.
戦闘妖精になったか 説明しろ！》
当医院は 歯の治療はもちろん➡
My XXXX will break.
二度と 虫歯にならぬよう
予防対策のｵﾍﾟも➡
Until my XXX collapses,
ｻｰﾋﾞｽとして行っているんです｡
《土方:だからそれ
もう 歯医者じゃねえだろ！》
I will XXX my XXX standing tall!
(中山)では ｺｰｽの説明をさせて
いただきます｡
There's nothing to be scared of.
歯の治療と改造手術が
ｾｯﾄになってるのが Ａｺｰｽ｡
Because you're here with me.
Ｂｺｰｽは 改造手術に ﾄﾞﾘﾝｸﾊﾞｰが付く
仕様となっております｡
I'm ready now.
《Ｂｺｰｽ！ もはや
歯の治療してねえだろ｡
なんで
ﾄﾞﾘﾝｸﾊﾞｰが付いてくんだよ!?》
So there won't be any turning back.
あのう すみません
改造手術はいいんで➡
歯の治療だけやってくれるｺｰｽは
ないんですか？
An indecisive big-wig can go to hell.
治療と改造 別々にｵｰﾀﾞｰするなら➡
ｾｯﾄのＡｺｰｽのほうが お得ですよ｡
いや だから➡
Because too much foul play
can get real dangerous.
改造手術はいらないんです｡
治療だけしたいんです｡
そうなると いちばん近いのは
ＺｺｰｽかＸｺｰｽですね｡
何なんですか？ それ｡
Now!
Screw regulations and keep rollin' on.
Ｚｺｰｽは歯の治療のほか
ﾘﾗｯｸｽﾏｯｻｰｼﾞがつきます｡
To a fresh and new world.
Ｘｺｰｽは
歯の治療に ｻﾗﾀﾞﾊﾞｰがつきますね｡
あ… あぁ
じゃあ ｵﾚ Ｚｺｰｽでいいです｡
Censorship can go suck it!
ﾘﾗｯｸｽﾏｯｻｰｼﾞがつくほうで｡
どうでもいいけど それで｡
ﾗｼﾞｬｰ｡
Who needs any brakes?
《あぁ よかった｡ なんとか
改造手術だけは免れたか》
Censorship can go suck it!
ﾍﾞﾃｨﾃﾞｽ｡ ﾖﾛｼｸ ｼｬﾁｮｻﾝ｡
I only follow what's in my heart.
《ﾏｯｻｰｼﾞ嬢つけられた～！
結局 改造されてんじゃねえか｡
Censorship can go suck it!
しかもこれ 虫歯予防も何も
まったく関係ねえだろ!?
全然 やる気ねえけど｡
Not my fault if the apology was rewritten.
せめて もう少しｸﾞﾚｰﾄﾞの高い娘➡
つけてくれても
よかったんじゃねえの！》
Censorship can go suck it!
(中山)解説しよう｡
移植した快楽要塞ﾍﾞﾃｨと➡
坂田さんは
神経までつながることにより➡
There's no turning back now.
本来ﾒｶである快楽要塞ﾍﾞﾃｨは
彼の目には➡
まるで
生身のﾏｯｻｰｼﾞ嬢のように映るのだ｡
I'll take everyone with me
when I die, necromancer!
当院のｻｰﾋﾞｽは完璧である｡
《危なかった！ 危うく ｵﾚも➡
あんなもん
つけられるところだった｡
Thank you Tsu Terakado-chan!
ﾊﾞｶめ｡
軽率に動けば痛い目を見るのは➡
We have two more lines left.
戦闘妖精の件で学習済みだ｡
The ninth and tenth place ones.
Ｘｺｰｽ！ 歯の治療にｻﾗﾀﾞﾊﾞｰがつく｡
こちらが正解だ》
Say, why did we start the
countdown from one?
Isn't it usually the other way around?
あの ｵﾚのほうは
Ｘｺｰｽでお願いします｡
ﾗｼﾞｬｰ｡
Right? Don't you love how
this show is fizzling out?
《ｻﾗﾀﾞﾊﾞｰなどというｼｽﾃﾑが
体につけられるわけもない｡
How we obviously didn't plan ahead...
Don't even feel like making
excuses anymore, huh?
ｸｸ… ありがとうよ｡
Ninth place is that usual one-liner.
ｷｻﾏのﾊﾞｶのおかげで
同じ轍を踏まずに済んだぜ》
Enjoy yourselves.
Count...
Down!
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #9]
《ｻ… ｻﾗﾀﾞ婆つけられた！
やられた！ ｻﾗﾀﾞﾊﾞｰって
ｻﾗﾀﾞ婆のことだったのか｡
Time to go, Gintoki.
つうか ｻﾗﾀﾞ婆って何!?
You're Zura..
ただ ｻﾗﾀﾞ食ってるだけの
ばばあじゃねえか！
Kotaro Zura?!
It's not Zura. It's Katsura!
しかも ﾏﾖではなくﾄﾞﾚｯｼﾝｸﾞ派かよ｡
最悪だ！
Let's do this, Zura.
こんな趣味の合わないばばあと
一生一緒に➡
It's not Zura. It's Katsura!
ｻﾗﾀﾞをつつき合わなければ
いけないのか！》
Right, Zura?
よし じゃあ下準備は
これくらいでいいですね｡
It's not Zura. It's Captain Katsura!
Oh, it's Zura.
《どんな準備だよ！ まったく
役に立ちそうにねえだろ!!》
It's not Zura. It's Katsura.
じゃあ本格的な治療 始めますね｡
It's not monk. It's Katsura.
It's not Zura. It's Katsura.
《歯の治療の前に
この体を治療しろ｡
It's not Zura. It's Zurako.
もとの体を返せ！》
It's not Zura. It's Katsura.
お口 あ～んしてください｡
It's not Zura. It's Katsura!
力抜いてください｡
怖いことなんて何もないですよ｡
It's not Zura. It's Katsura!
It's not Fruit Punch Samurai. It's Katsura!
《お前が怖いんだよ！》
口を大きく開けてくださいね｡
It's not part-timer. It's Katsura.
It's not you. It's Katsura.
ﾄﾞﾘﾙに触れたら
顔 吹き飛びますよ｡
It's not Zura. It's Matsu (Pine Tree).
《そんな でけえﾄﾞﾘﾙ
口に入るわけねえだろ！》
It's not Zura. It's Katsura.
It's not kid. It's Katsura.
安心してください｡
改造によって あなたたちの体は➡
I'm not Lupin, I'm Zura.
Oops, I mean Katsura.
治療の負担が
軽減されるようになってます｡
It's not Mr. K. It's Katsura.
It's not Mr. K. Zura. It's Katsura.
どうですか？
あまり痛みを感じないでしょ？
It's not ****, it's Katsura!
It's not Zura. It's Katsura.
《言われてみれば…》
It's not crap, it's Mayuzom.
《痛みを まったく感じないぞ》
It's not rap, it's Katsu-rap.
(中山)当医院は 迅速な治療が
売りとなっていますが➡
It's not Mario. It's Katsura.
患者の身には
それだけ負担もかかるのです｡
It's not Zura, it's Katsuo.
(ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝ)改造手術を推し進めるのは
まず患者の皆さまに➡
It's not Capt. Tsuba, it's Captain Katsura.
治療に耐えうる体に
なってもらい➡
It's not Master. It's Katsura.
安全に治療を進めるためでも
あるのです｡
It's not Zura. It's Katsura.
《いや 安全っていうか➡
I'm not okay and it's Katsura.
改造されてる時点で
安全もｸｿもないからね》
It's not Zura, it's Ka-
《２人:っていうか これ➡
全部 あっちに
いってるだけじゃねえか!?》
It's not Zura. It's Katsura.
(ｼｬｻﾞｰﾝ)痛みは ほぼ彼女たちが
肩代わりしてくれるんで➡
It's not Zura-chi. I'm Ill Smith.
安心して治療を受けてください｡
Enough already!
《土方:いや 尋常な苦しみ方じゃ
ないんですけど｡
How many times does he need
to introduce himself?!
とても 安心して
見てられないんですけど》
It stopped making sense
about halfway through.
(中山)彼女たちがいなければ
この苦しみが➡
Like a guest that barfs and falls.
もろに皆さんを
襲っていたんですよ｡
Don't you mean Gestaltzerfall?
《痛み感じてないだけで
あんな状態になるようなこと➡
Well, only the tenth place one is left.
されてるの!?
大丈夫なの？ ねぇ！
Whose line will take the last spot?
あの…
やめて そんな目で見ないで｡
Man, I can't wait to see.
なに!?
ｵﾚが悪いの？ ｵﾚがﾀﾞﾒなの？》
I sense a glimmer of hope now that
we're down to the tenth spot.
Then here's the final best line!
《ｵﾚのせいじゃないよね｡
違うよね？ 関係ないよね？》
Count...
Down!
《あ… あれ？ 何これ？
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #10]
なんか変なﾋﾞｼﾞｮﾝが
頭に流れ込んでくるよ｡
何これ？
ねぇ 走馬灯じゃねえの!?
Give me a break, Mom...
Today's Sunday.
あれ… もしかして
ﾍﾞﾃｨの走馬灯じゃねえの!?
Yer such a moron!
Today is Tuesday!
つうか
なに勝手に記憶捏造してんの？
You nitwit...
What if the Anti-Foreigner Faction stormed
this place while you were goofing off?!
お前と こんな覚えねえよ!!
やめろ 妙なもん見せんじゃねえ！
Take this job seriously.
ｵﾚは何も悪くねえ ｵﾚ関係ねえし！
When do I ever not take
this job seriously?
改造されて迷惑してんの
こっちだし!!》
The only one I never take seriously
is you, Hijikata-san!
《あれ 何だこれ？
Wait! You again?!
妙な映像が
勝手に頭に流れ込んでくる｡
Right? You can't hold one
of these without me.
おい これ… 走馬灯!?
ｻﾗﾀﾞ婆の走馬灯？
Bastard...
Do you have any idea how many complaints we got from
the fans when you did a voice-over on Takasugi?!
つうかｻﾗﾀﾞ婆 ろくな思い出ねえ!!
ｻﾗﾀﾞとの絡みしかねえ！
Two?
ｻﾗﾀﾞ婆 いいのか これで？
ろくな思い出ないままで｡
Are you kidding me?!
This is bad, Gin-san.
いや いい｡ ｵﾚは歯を治すんだ｡
It just had to be Okita-san!
ｻﾗﾀﾞ婆なんて
知ったこっちゃねえんだ!!》
Shinpachi, my tummy's starting to hurt.
《２人:ｵﾚは悪くない
ｵﾚは悪くない ｵﾚは悪くない…｡
I might need to go barf and fall.
Ah!
Hold on, Kagura-chan!
ｵﾚのせいじゃない
ｵﾚのせいじゃない…｡
Shinpachi, I'll let you handle this.
What? Hey!
そうさ
ｵﾚたちは 何にも悪くな～い!!》
Hold on!
Uh, how am I supposed to end this?
Allow me to handle this.
あの～ すみません
ｳﾁ歯医者じゃないんですけど…｡
No worries.
Then I'll present my own version of
the best GinTama lines ranking.
知ってますよ｡
Count...
Down!
いや でも その症状は
どう見ても虫歯でしょ｡
What?!
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #10]
早く歯医者に行ったほうが…｡
The only one I never take seriously
is you, Hijikata-san!
いや もう虫歯はいいんです｡
そのうち腐って落ちますから｡
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #9]
It's not Zura. It's Katsura!
じゃあ何しにきたんですか？
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #8]
Until my body collapses, I will
live my life standing tall!!
(２人)彼女を なおしてください｡
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #7]
My soul will break.
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #6]
But if I don't do anything now,
I won't be able to live with myself.
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #5]
But anywhere within reach of my sword,
is my country.
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #4]
It'll take more than a blow like
that...to break my soul!
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #3]
If you've got enough time to fantasize
about your beautiful death,
why don't you live your life
beautifully to the end?
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #2]
I just want the girl I love to be happy.
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking #1]
Then, and now, what I protect
has never changed!!
[Best GinTama Lines Ranking Hall of Fame]
Bansai.
You can't get attuned to my song?
Yay, yay...
Now this is just ugly.
[Preview]
It existed long ago...
The ceiling may have been shut,
but the moon existed back then.
A small, brave, and beautiful moon.
["It's Bad Luck to See a Spider at Night"]
[The heavens open. Moonlight shining,
back to Yoshiwara...]
[...he returns.]
[See you next time.]
＜改ざんＢ－ＣＡＳカードによる
不正視聴は➡
刑法により禁じられた犯罪行為＞
＜５年以下の懲役 または➡
50万円以下の
罰金に処せられます＞
＜後悔しても 元には戻せない＞
不正視聴!?